=Episode 3=
Xi Yuan, set the carrier pigeon aside.
Surrender yourself.
Your Highness,
I'm just eating a roasted pigeon.
That's not a crime, is it?
(Boy-crazy and a glutton.)
Your Highness,
the message is almost completely burned.
Did we misjudge her?
Your Highness,
want a drumstick?
Hey!
Eating on duty?
Go clean the Archive Pavilion.
Don't come back
until it's spotless.
Get moving!
(You took my pigeon.)
The Treasure Pavilion is
a highly classified military site,
housing countless treasures and
ancient texts.
Obtaining even one
would be a merit above all others.
That's brilliant, Your Highness.
If that girl is a Huangyan spy,
she'll definitely slip up.
What?
A personal handmaiden?
Why does His Highness
care so much about protecting
that wretched lowborn woman?
My lady, fret not.
With your strength,
I'm sure you'll make Xi Yuan
embarrass herself
on the day of the martial trial.
Am I supposed to wait until that day
and watch His Highness go easy on her?
You're right, my lady.
Once she's dead,
her name will be forgotten.
Let's see how she competes with me then.
The Huyun Imperial Palace is massive,
and the Archive Pavilion
has nothing but a single table?
What's there even to clean?
All done.
How...
How am I supposed to clean this?
Jin Yunlie,
you set me up!
Your Highness.
What is it?
She showed no interest in the maps
and military documents we planted.
At first she was cleaning seriously.
Then...
She fell asleep.
(A glutton and a sleepyhead.)
(I should've known this silly girl
couldn't be a spy.)
(But why doesn't she remember her past?)
(Did she lose her memory?)
(Perhaps it's for the best.)
(She's a little dumb,)
(a bit slow,)
(but also a bit)
(endearing.)
Ouch!
That hurts.
Why would Huangyan send
such a dim-witted person as a spy?
Symbiotic Bond.
A legendary symbiotic spell
bestowed by deities.
When two people truly in love
form this bond,
they become linked to each other.
From then on,
their love becomes vitality.
Whenever one is wounded and bleeding,
pressing foreheads together
allows them to heal each other.
A Symbiotic Bond meant to
exist between deities...
Why has it been confirmed
between the two of us?
♪I shut out the world, you're all I see♪
♪One glance to last forever,
just you and me♪
♪Though deep in bone this longing stays,
a few more glances cast♪
♪An everlasting love to hold,
forever made to last♪
So it was fate all along.
You didn't come to Huyun for Huangyan,
you came for me.
I made you some mung bean cakes.
Try one.
♪Once the heart knows love's design♪
♪It's you I seek, and intertwine♪
Wait.
(Is she trying to
conquer my stomach first?)
Alright now.
Since I've been behaving
pretty well lately,
could you teach me a few moves?
We'll see.
So stubborn.
How unbelievable!
Fine, I don't care.
No way I can't learn on my own.
Let me think.
How do they do it in those dramas?
Tidal Crash!
Tidal Crash again!
Ha!
Are...
Are you alright?
He's fine.
As for you...
Wh...
What?
I'll teach you to cultivate.
I begged you before and you wouldn't.
Why so generous now?
Naturally, His Highness is merciful.
He'd rather you not die in the arena.
You talk too much.
Your Spirit Core just opened.
Start with the absolute basics.
Got it!
Feel the flow of Spiritual Energy
within you.
Gather it here.
The Spiritual Energy in your dantian
will circulate throughout your body.
Do you feel it?
Nope.
Here,
and here,
is all the path
the Spirit Energy must take
to burst through your fingertips.
Alright.
Now, follow this force.
Channel your Spiritual Power
to your fingertips.
♪I shut out the world, you're all I see♪
♪One glance to last forever,
just you and me♪
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Focus.
Alright.
♪After the world fades away,
you alone stay in my sight♪
♪Rouge sachets and jade towers
can't match your dance in the light♪
♪Once the heart knows love's design♪
An average cultivator
needs at least three months
just to gather Spiritual Energy.
To attack with a Spirit Sphere,
it'd take about a year of practice.
Your Spirit Core just opened.
Don't rush.
With time
and enough practice,
you'll surely...
Look!
I did it!
Not bad.
Keep going.
On it!
Don't rush.
Channel it.
Right.
♪Who can forget the dreams
once held and lost♪
♪Petals on your shoulder reveal your charm♪
♪For whom does the wind shift so quiet♪
♪That is my silent confession in bloom♪
♪I shut out the world, you're all I see♪
Wow!
Look!
Am I awesome or what?
♪Though deep in bone this longing stays♪
♪A few more glances cast♪
♪An everlasting love to hold,
forever made to last♪
♪After the world fades away,
you alone stay in my sight♪
♪Rouge sachets and jade towers
can't match your dance in the light♪
♪Once the heart knows love's design,
it's you I seek♪
♪And intertwine♪
You have talent,
but if you can't use it effectively,
you may not gain the upper hand
in the arena.
Yeah.
I have some matters to attend to today.
Wait.
What is this?
This is a Whispering Bell.
Infuse just a little Spiritual Power,
and you can call me
anytime, anywhere.
So it's basically a phone
in the cultivation world?
Where is he?
Your Highness,
your mother left you
the Whispering Bell.
You just gave it to her?
(Xi Yuan,)
(since you came here
wholeheartedly for me,)
(I will protect you for a lifetime.)
(Longyuan Kingdom)
(Qing Yuluo, Longyuan's Second Prince)
Great Demon Lord,
I have delivered your blood
to the Xia family as instructed.
They can coordinate with us from within.
Once we get the Xuanji Jade,
then
you will be able to descend
upon this world once more.
Great Demon Lord?
It seems
the Great Demon Lord's power
is still very weak right now.
I will
leave you to recover in peace.
Once the task is complete,
I will report back.
Spiritual Power rises from the dantian,
and circulates throughout the body.
Next,
practice my attack.
Watch out!
It's you?
What do you want?
Keep watch.
Understood.
When I first met you,
we got off on the wrong foot.
So I
have come here specially
to make amends.
This pill boosts Spiritual Power.
I know your difficulties,
so I've come to give you
this Spirit Pill.
Since when are you so kind?
I don't buy it.
Well, you're not as dumb as you look.
Please.
At least I've watched 76 episodes
of The Legend of Zhen Huan.
You think I'd fall for
a cheap trick like this?
Goodbye now.
What are you doing?
You brought this on yourself,
Xi Yuan.
Here.
Open your mouth.
Not cooperating?
Oh my,
I...
I forgot to mention,
if you take too many of these pills,
your body will explode.
(Hall of Longevity, Martial Trial)
I...
I yield!
Miss Liu is defeated!
Miss Xia Honglian
advances to the final duel!
It seems the position of Crown Princess
will surely belong to Miss Xia Honglian.
Then you
will be the father-in-law
of the Crown Prince.
Oh my,
you flatter me.
The title matters little.
What matters is being able
to assist His Highness.
Ah yes,
the Crown Prince
is still young after all.
His experience in statecraft
is somewhat lacking.
Is that so?
Minister Xia,
are you already pondering
how to instruct me in the future?
I wouldn't dare.
Greetings, Your Highness!
Have you found her?
Your Highness,
could she have chickened out
and run away?
Announce the results.
I hereby declare
Miss Xia Honglian
has won sixteen consecutive matches
in under half an hour,
thus claiming the martial trial.
Hold on!
Xi Yuan?
Miss Xia,
I'm sorry
to disappoint you.
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit,♪
♪the envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions,♪
♪leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road,♪
♪I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain,♪
♪forever beyond redemption♪